## Nguyễn Hải Đăng

**DOB** 19-10-1991

**Gender** Male

**Phone** 0977484002

Email haidang@cnttbk.com

Address Lane 13 Khuat Duy Tien, Thanh Xuan, Ha Noi

Website https://haidang.me

### **CARREER OBJECTIVES**

Desiring to be a professional and skillful developer in order to prove myself in the opening and developing age of Technology.

Being able to find a good position with modern and active working environment that helps me to do specialized and professional projects.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

11 / 2015 - now	FUNIX University Python
2 / 2014 - 10/2015	Minh Chau Entertainment Joinstock Company Developer iOS SDK game, Web server API, PHP Developer,
6 / 2013 - 1/2014	Tinh Van Incubator Leader PHP Developer,
1 / 2012 - 4/2012	Hanoi University of science and technology Participating in scientific research about data mining

### **EDUCATION**

09/2009 - 05/2015	Hanoi University of science and technology
	Information Systems

### **CERTIFICATIONS AND AWARDS**

2012	Being the co-author of the scientific article: "Improving Vietnamese web
	page clustering by combining neighbors' content and using iterative feature selection". Detail in: http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2350726

### **SKILLS**

Programming languages	- PHP - Objective C - C / C++ - Python - Java - NodeJS
Frameworks	<ul> <li>Codeigniter</li> <li>Laravel 4.x / 5.x</li> <li>Django</li> <li>FuelPHP</li> <li>Phalcon</li> </ul>
Databases	<ul><li>- MySQL</li><li>- MongoDB</li><li>- Redis</li><li>- MariaDB</li><li>- SQL Server</li></ul>
Operating Systems	- Mac OS X - Windows 7, 8 - Ubuntu - Centos
IDE	- PHPStorm - XCode - AppCode - PyCharm - WebStorm - Virtual studio 2010 - Netbeans - Eclipse
Web servers	<ul><li>Nginx</li><li>Apache 2</li><li>Tomcat 6, 7</li><li>NodeJS</li></ul>

## DỰ ÁN

### Staff management website

(01 / 2012 - 06 / 2012)

Customer	Hanoi University of science and technology
Description	Taking part in the project of upgrading staff management system of Hanoi University

	of Science and Technology.
Team size	5
My position	Team leader
My responsibility	Build backend
Technologies used	PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3

# Staff management website (10 / 2012 - 01 / 2013)

Customer	National college of Education
Description	Establishing the staff management system of National college of Education
Team size	2
My position	Team leader
My responsibility	Do everything
Technologies used	PHP, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3

### **MCID**

(05 / 2014 - 02 / 2015)

Customer	MC-Corp
Description	https://mcid.vn
Team size	2
My position	Member
My responsibility	Backend, API
Technologies used	PHP Laravel 4.2, Phalcon, MySQL, MongoDB, Redis

**iOS SDK game** (05 / 2014 - 10 / 2014)

Customer	MC-Corp
Description	iOS SDK game
Team size	1
My position	Member
My responsibility	Do everything
Technologies used	Objective C